mixamo.com 2015-04-21

# Privacy - Mixamo

**IE 8 and less is not supported by Mixamo.** Please use [FireFox](http://www.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/new/) or [Chrome](https://www.google.com/chrome/) or a newer version of IE to use this website. 

##  **Mixamo, Inc. Privacy Policy**

Last updated August 17, 2012

Mixamo, Inc. respects your right to privacy and we believe any information you provide to us should be protected from unauthorized disclosure to third parties. This Privacy Policy statement describes how information we collect on the Mixamo.com website is used and shared with third parties. By using the Mixamo website or providing any personally identifiable information through the Mixamo website, you agree to the practices described in this policy. This policy applies to anonymous data and personal information collected at the Mixamo website. This policy also applies to personally identifiable customer information collected in connection with the sale, use, and support of the Mixamo services available on the Mixamo website (Services). If you do not consent to this Privacy Policy, do not use or download any materials from the Mixamo website. 

###  1\. What Types of Information We Collect. 

#### Personally Identifiable Information. 

We collect personally identifiable information through our website. This information is used in e-commerce transactions and to provide customer service and support. Our website collects personally identifiable information at several points, including processes associated with password registration, license acceptance, feedback, purchasing services, account creation and e-mail opt-in (Personally Identifiable Information). Visitors may voluntarily provide (and we will collect) information including: name, email address, billing information, and purchase information.

#### Cookies. 

Mixamo’s website uses cookies. We use cookies in order to better understand our website visitors’ needs. A cookie is a small text file (which includes a unique identifier) that our server places on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies enable us to track use patterns, repeat visitors, and deliver customized content to website users.

#### Log Files. 

Like most standard website servers we also use log files. Log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use (Engagement Data). IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

If you do not want us to use your information as described in this Section 1, please follow the procedure in Section 3 (Changing Your Information; Opt Out Procedures) below.

In order to protect the privacy interests of younger Internet users, we do not actively market our websites or Services to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13 for marketing purposes. We encourage children of any age to visit our website or to use our Services only with parental supervision.

###  2\. What We Do With The Information We Collect. 

We use information we collect to understand how our customers are using our website and Services in order to improve them.

#### Data Analysis. 

We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate visitor behavior. This allows us to measure relative visitor interest in the various pages of our website and to improve the design of our website. Such aggregated information is not linked to personally identifiable information. Anonymous, aggregated data is analyzed to understand how customers use our Services and to assist in the design of future Services.

#### Personally Identifiable Information. 

Personal information is used to fulfill purchase transactions, provide customer support, and for marketing purposes such as email announcements of new services or offers. We provide an option for you to choose not to receive marketing communications in Section 3 (Changing Your Information; Opt Out Procedures) below.

#### Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information. 

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information collected on our website. We use third parties (including contractors and service providers) to help with certain aspects of providing the Services to you, which may require disclosure of your personal information to them. For example, we may use a third party to communicate with you (via telephone, email, or letter) about our Services, to send information to you, to process and collect payment via your credit card (if applicable), and to perform services that we outsource. We require these contractors and third parties to use your personal information only as necessary to perform these services.

#### Links. 

We offer links to third party websites. Please note that those other websites may have privacy practices that are different from ours and the collection and use of your personal information if you follow those links will be governed by the privacy policies on those other sites.

#### Posting. 

Our website may offer a space for postings and submissions. You agree that any information you post in these spaces will be publicly available, non-confidential, and non-proprietary to you.

#### Information Shared with Autodesk. 

If you have accessed our website through a product or service of Autodesk, Inc. (Autodesk), such as Autodesk 3ds Max Design software, we are required to share your Personally Identifiable Information and Engagement Data with Autodesk. We understand that Autodesk will use such data in accordance with its own privacy policy, which is available at: www.autodesk.com/privacy.

#### Information Shared with Stanford University. 

If you have downloaded the free application on the Mixamo website that is jointly marked as a Mixamo and Stanford University product, we are required to share all end-user data with respect to such application with Stanford, including the usage patterns, user feedback, and other derivative data based on such original usage data.

### 3\. Changing Your Information; Opt Out Procedure.

#### Changing Your Information. 

If you wish to correct or delete any of your personal information stored by us or change the way we use your information, please contact support at support@mixamo.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to fulfill your request in a timely manner, but not more than 30 days. Even if we delete such personal information from its ‘live’ database, it may still be stored on other databases (including those kept for archival purposes).

#### Opting-out. 

Users who no longer wish to receive communications from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with “unsubscribe” in the subject line of the e-mail. You may also opt-out of these communications by sending an e-mail to support@mixamo.com specifying that you no longer want to receive communications from us.

We reserve the right to use your contact information if we consider it necessary to send you crucial information about the Services you have purchased from us. Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personally identifiable information when required by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us. In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to protect the personal safety of users, our website, or the public. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in the event of a merger, consolidation, or sale of all or substantially all of our assets.

### 4\. Security.

We use industry-standard methods of securing our electronic databases of personal information. Except as provided elsewhere in this privacy policy, we limit access to personal information in electronic databases to those persons in our organization who have a business need for such access. You should know however that no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks associated with personal information. Your privacy is very important to us. Due to factors beyond our control, however, we cannot fully ensure that your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties other than those mentioned above. For example, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

### 5\. Updates to this Privacy Policy.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended version on our website.

### 6\. Contact Us.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact support@mixamo.com.
